Guide to the Jim Graham papers, 1961-2015 MS2013
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Jim Graham/Whitman-Walker Clinic records, 1973-1998; MS2013 Series 1
  - Administrative files, 1980-1998; MS2013 Series 1 Subseries 3
    - Burial Law Coalition, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Capitol Communications, March 24, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - CARE (Comprehensive AIDS Resources and Education Consortium) Coalition, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Caseloads, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Center for Disease Control (CDC), undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Certificates of Occupancy, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Chambers, David, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Chan Sam and Associates, Inc., undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Chirac Visit, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Chronological file, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Church Association for Community Services Division of AIDS Ministries, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Circle of 6, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Circle of 6, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Burroughs and Welcome, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Circle of 6 Board Presidents, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Circle of 6- Burroughs and Welcome, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Citicorp-Kilbourne, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - City Contract, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Claim for Interest, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Clinton Visit, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Collective Bargaining Agreement, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Collective Bargaining Proposals, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Coming Home Hospice Capital Campaign Budget, 1985-1987 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Commission of Public Health Handbook, September, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Committees- Lists of all Members, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Communications, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Community Development Block Grant, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Community HIV/AIDS Advisory Committee, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Community Research, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Concerned Citizens on Alcohol and Drug Abuse, Inc., 1992 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Consulting and Services Agreement, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Contract Payments Log, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Contracts I, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Contracts II, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Contracts, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Corporate Registrations, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Corporate Relations, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1992 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1995-1998 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, n.d., undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence Files- Dusty Cunningham's File, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence Files- Dusty Cunningham's File, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Declaration (Maryland) Form, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Declaration (Virginia) Form, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Dedication of Elizabeth Taylor Medical Center, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Department of Housing and Community Development (DHCHD) Information, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Department of Human Services, HIV/AIDS Epidemic Selected Sentinel Survey, May, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Desk Plan, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Dessert, Mark, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Development, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Development Plan, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Digest, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Digest of Whitman-Walker Clinic Policies, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Director of Communications, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Director's Meeting, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - District of Columbia (D.C.) AIDS Advisory Committee I, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - D.C. AIDS Advisory Committee II, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - D.C. AIDS Advisory Committee III, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - D.C. AIDS Education and Training Center, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - D.C. AIDS/R.F.P. I, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - D.C. AIDS/R.F.P. II, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - D.C. AIDS/R.F.P. III, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - D.C. Alcoholism, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - D.C. Contract BIG, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - D.C. Contracts- JA 93597, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - D.C. Directory- HIV Services, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - D.C. Government Contracts, Department of Human Services, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - D.C. Government Contracts, Department of Human Services, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - D.C. Government Contracts, Department of Human Services I, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - D.C. Government Contracts, Department of Human Services II, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - D.C. Government Relations, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - D.C. Property- AIDS Fiscal Year, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - D.C. Tax Exempt Certificate, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Dixon HIV Transitions I, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Dixon HIV Transitions II, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Dixon HIV Transitions III, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Dr. Lovelace, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Drug Testing, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Efficiency and Effectiveness Task Force Recommendations, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Elizabeth Taylor Center Designs, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Emergency Weather Guidance, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Employee Assistance Program, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Employee Health Insurance, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Employment Law, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Evans Fund-raising, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Executive Directors Counterparts, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Expansion of Clinic Medical Services, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Eydie Whittington, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Facilities Maintenance, 1988-1996 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - February Monthly Report, Commission of Public Health, Sunnye Sherman AIDS Education Services, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Fendall Street Apartment Building, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Fendall Street Apartments, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Final Report on the Mayor's Task Force on Health Care Reform, May, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Final Report of the Mayor's Blue Ribbon Panel on Health Care Reform Implementation, February, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Finance and Development, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Finances, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Financial Information, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Financial Report, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Financial Statements, Audit Report I, September 30, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Financial Statements, Audit Report II, September 30, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Financial Statements, 1984-1990 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Financial Statements, March, April, May, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Financial Statements, July, August, October, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Financial Statements, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Food and Friends, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Foodbank, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Foundation of Pharmacists and Corporate America and AIDS Education, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Foundations, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Fourth Annual Spring Gala- Red Hot Riviera, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Free Clinic Assistance Program Act, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Friends for Life Gala, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Friends for Life Gala II, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Friends for Life Gala Budget, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Friends for Life Gala Logistics, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Friends for Life Spring Gala Benefit Committee Meeting #1, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Funderburke, Eugene, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Fund-raiser, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Fundraiser for Charlene Drew Jarvis, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Fund-raising Agreement, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Gamache, Mike- Correspondence File, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Gay and Lesbian Hotline, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC) Client Conduct Policy Draft, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Gay Men's Venereal Disease Clinic, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Gay Men's Outreach and Sex Education, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - General Files I, 1978-1980 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - General Files II, 1978-1980 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - General Ledger I, 1980-1984 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - General Ledger II, 1980-1984 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Gilbertson House Lease, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Grainger, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Harvey, Jim- Correspondence File, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Haymaker Group, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Health Care Reform, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Health Care Reform II, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Health Insurance I, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Health Insurance II, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Health Insurance III, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Health Insurance Information, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Hepatitis B- Public Service Information, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Hepatitis B Vaccine Testing- Public Service Information, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - High Risk For AIDS- Homosexual/Bisexual Males, IV Drug Abusers, and Prostitutes - Cost Proposal, April 22, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - High Risk For AIDS- Homosexual/Bisexual Male Population - Cost Proposal and Technical Proposal, March 12, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - HIV/AIDS Prevention-Education Policy, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - HIV Home Testing Funding, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - HIV Prevention Plan, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - HIV Testing/Counseling, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Home Testing- HIV I, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Home Testing- HIV II, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Housing and Care Services, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Housing and Care Services II, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Housing Directories, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - HUD Occupancy Task Force I, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - HUD Occupancy Task Force II, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - HUD Occupancy Task Force III, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - HUD Occupancy Task Force IV, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - HUD Occupancy Task Force V, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Human Resources Committee, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Impact- D.C., undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Improper Patient Care Allegations, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - In Service Training, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - In the News, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Independence Federal Savings, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Infusion Therapy, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Institute for Social Security Report, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Insurance- J6, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Insurances and Policies, undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Inventory File, undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - IRS Letter, undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Interagency Task Force on AIDS, undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Jarvis, Charlene Drew, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Jeffrey David Clopper Fund, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - JENCO, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Jones, Bill T., undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Kalorama Relocation Effort, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Kalorama Road Building, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Kalorama Road Building II, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Kalorama Road Building Dedication, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Karpawich Litigation, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Lab License, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Latino Operating Committee, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - LCC Proposed Documents, undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Lease Agreements, September 24, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Lease Agreement- Building 1802, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Lease/ Housing, undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Legal Forms, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Legal Papers I, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Legal Papers II, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Legal Services Referral List, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Lesbian Services Program, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Lewis Advertising, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Lists- Various Committees and Programs, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Local Contracts, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Long Distance Planning Committee, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Long Range Planning Committee, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Long Range Planning Statement, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Loose Papers- AIDS in the Workplace, Adult Children of Alcoholics, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Management Assistance Group, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Maryland Suburbs, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Massage Therapy, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Mayor's Blue Ribbon Panel I, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Mayor's Blue Ribbon Panel II, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Mayor's Blue Ribbon Panel III, undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Mayor's Blue Ribbon Panel on Health Care Reform Implementation- Final Report, February, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Mayor's Blue Ribbon Panel on Health Care Reform (Work Group Minutes), undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Mayor's Blue Ribbon Task Force on Health Care Reform, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Mayor's Task Force on Health Care Reform, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Mayor's Task Force on Health Care Reform II, undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Mayor's Task Force on Health Care Reform III, undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Mayor's Task Force on Health Care Reform IV, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Mayor's Task Force on Health Care Reform V, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Mayor's Task Force on Health Care Reform VI, undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - MCL Information Maximum Capacity Level, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - McCormack and Associates, undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - McKinney House, undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - "Medicaid Managed Care: How Do Community Centers Fit In", in Health Care Review, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Medical Directories, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Medical Services, undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Member List- Washington Area Consortium on HIV Infection in Youth, undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Mental Health Services, undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Metropolitan Statistics, "AIDS in Washington D.C.,", 1990-1991 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Information on Non-Profit Boards, undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Mortgage, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - National Association of People With AIDS (NAPWA), undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - National Alliance of Lesbian and Gay Health Clinics, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force (NGLTF), 1994 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Nations Bank, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Neeme, Suzanne, undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Newsletter, undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Newsletters, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Newspaper Articles, undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - NIH/CIRID Proposal, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - NITA Site Visit, February 10, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Nominations/BID, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Non-Profit Board Reports, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Northern Virginia Whitman-Walker Clinic AIDS Program, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Northern Virginia HIV Consortium Case Management Project, June 29, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Northern Virginia Project, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Northern Virginia Project, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Numbers- Maryland, undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Numbers- National, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Numbers- Virginia, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Office of Latino Affairs, undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Office of Management Budget (OMB)- Staff of OMB Tour, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - OPSCOM Manual, 1979-1980 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - OPSCOM Manual II, 1979-1980 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - OPSCOM Meeting Minutes and Correspondence I, 1980-1984 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - OPSCOM Meeting Minutes and Correspondence II, 1980-1984 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Paper on Gays and Bisexuals in Washington, D.C., Circa 1987 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Personnel Policies (Non-Collective Bargaining Unit Members), undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Personnel/Administration, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Personnel Policies and Procedures Manual, Draft, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Policies and Procedures Manual, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Personnel Policies and Procedures Manual, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Personnel Policy, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Poland, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Policies Group- Alcoholism Services/Director and Counselor, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Policies Group- Articles of Incorporation and Registered Agent, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Policies Group- Clinic Administrator, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Policies Group- Consolidation Agreement, undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Policies Group- Gay Hotline, undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Policies Group- GCDB/Alcoholism Services, undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Policies Group- G.W.U. Medical Services Affiliation, undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Policies Group- GMVDC Manager, undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Policies Group-Interpretation of At-Large Board Seats, undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Policies Group- IRS and District of Columbia Tax Exempt Documents, undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Policies Group- Lesbian Health Counseling Center (LHCC), undated (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Policies Group- Loan Policy, undated (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Policies Group- Medical Director/Medical Technologist, undated (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Policies Group- OPSCOM/GMVDC, undated (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Policies Group-Personnel Policy and Contracts, undated (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Policies Group- Policy on Clinic Vehicles, undated (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Policies Group- Research Committee, undated (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Policies Group- Quality Control Committee, undated (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Policies Group-Settlement of 17th Street Debt, undated (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Policies Group- Spending Policy, undated (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Policy Digest Revision, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Policy Digest Revision II, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Porter/Novelli, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Position Description- AIDS Program, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Power of Attorney and Temporary Guardianship Form, undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Press Clippings, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Press Clippings II, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Press Clippings, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Press Packet, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Prevention Campaign, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Prevention Materials, undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Program Committee, September, 1995, undated (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Program/Service Descriptions, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Project Abstract, undated (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Project NOVA, undated (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Project Summary for 1335 R Street, NW, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Property Maintenance, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - [A] Proposal to Conduct an AIDS Health Promotion Risk Reduction Program for Two Groups at High Risk for AIDS I-V Drug Abusers and Prostitutes, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Proposal to Robert Wood Johnson Foundation- Case Management Approach, undated (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Public Benefit Corporation Board Faxes, undated (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Publication of Annual Report Photo, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Quality Assurance, undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Quality Control: Screeners, Lab, Phlebotomy, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Rath, Duane, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Real Estate Title, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Realty Inc., 1993 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Report on Patient Services, October, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Response to Audit Report, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Risk Reduction Campaign, undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Risk Reduction Program for Gay and Bisexual Men, Including I-V Drug Users and Prostitutes, August 20, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Risk Reduction Program for Gay and Bisexual Men, Including I-V Drug Users and Prostitutes- Bound Copies, August 20, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Ryan White Title I Award, undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Safe Place Outreach Ministries, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Sample Executive Director Contract, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Sankofa/Abundant Life, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Savannah Street Lease- General Information, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Schools I, undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Schools II, undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Schools III, undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Schwartz House, 1984-1985 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Schwartz (Robert N.Schwartz, M.D.) House Board of Trustees, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Schwartz House Legal Leases, undated (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Schwartz Housing, undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Schwartz Housing Services, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Schwartz Housing Services, undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Second National Conference on Drug Abuse, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Services Descriptions, undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Sexual Behavior Research, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Sheridan Group, undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Shooting Up and AIDS, undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Skills Building, undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Speeches I, undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Speeches II, undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Speeches III, undated (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Statistics- Buddy Program, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Substance Abuse Prevention, Treatment, and Rehabilitation Service for the Gay Community I, undated (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Substance Abuse Prevention, Treatment, and Rehabilitation Service for the Gay Community II, undated (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Substance Abuse Prevention, Treatment, and Rehabilitation Service for the Gay Community III, undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Substance Abuse Prevention, Treatment, and Rehabilitation Service for the Gay Community IV, undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Survey of Five Health Clinics Owned by the District of Columbia, undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Sunnye Sherman AIDS Education, undated (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Task Force on AIDS, undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Tax Exemption Information, undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Teaming Agreement, undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Teen AIDS, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Telephone Procedures, undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Tenant Assistance Program (T.A.P.), undated (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Testimony, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Testimony Before Pres.Commission HIV, undated (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Testimony of the Non-Profit Clinic Consortium Public Benefits Corporation, undated (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - "Thailand?s AIDS Crisis," in The Washington Post, Tuesday, March 31, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - "The Way Back: The Stories of Gay and Lesbian Alcoholics," Third edition, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Transition Team Barry I, undated (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Transition Team Barry II, undated (Box 37, Folder 1)